// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let englishquestions = [

    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "The small child does whatever his father was done.",
        answer: "does",
        options: [
            "has done",
            "did",
            "does",
            "had done"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "You need not come unless you want to.",
        answer: "You don't need to come unless you want to",
        options: [
            "You don't need to come unless you want to",
            "You come only when you want to",
            "You come unless you don't want to",
            "You needn't come until you don't want to"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "The man to who I sold my house was a cheat.",
        answer: "to whom I sold",
        options: [
            "who was sold to",
            "to whom I sell",
            "to whom I sold",
            "No correction required"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "They were all shocked at his failure in the competition.",
        answer: "No correction required",
        options: [
            "were shocked at all",
            "had been all shocked on",
            "No correction required",
            "had all shocked at"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "He is too important for tolerating any delay.",
        answer: "to tolerate",
        options: [
            "to tolerate",
    "to tolerating",
    "at tolerating",
    "with tolerating"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "In addition to enhanced their reputations through strategic use of philanthropy, companies are sponsoring social initiatives to open new markets.",


            answer: "to enhancing their reputation",
    options: [
            "of enhancing their reputation",
    "to having enhance their reputation",
    "to enhancing their reputation",
    "No correction required"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The intruder stood quietly for few moments",
    answer: "for a few moments",
    options: [
            "for few time",
    "for the few moments",
    "for moments",
    "for a few moments"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Acquisition of certain specific skills can be facilitated from general awareness, education to novel situations",
    answer: "can be facilitated by",
    options: [
            "can be facilitated by",
    "may facilitate through",
    "can be felicitated with",
    "may be felicitated with"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "She cooks, washes dishes, does her homework and then relaxing.",
    answer: "then relaxes",
    options: [
            "then relaxes",
    "relaxing then",
    "then is relaxing",
    "then relaxes"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "He found the gold coin as he cleans the floor.",
    answer: "while cleaning",
    options: [
            "as he had cleaned",
    "while he cleans",
    "which he is cleaning",
    "while cleaning"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Despite his best efforts to conceal his anger ......",
    answer: "people came to know that he was annoyed",
    options: [
            "people came to know that he was annoyed",
    "we could detect that he was very happy",
    "he failed to give us an impression of his agony",
    "he succeeded in camouflaging his emotions"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Even if it rains I shall come means ......",
    answer: "I will certainly come whether it rains or not",
    options: [
            "if it rains I shall not come",
    "if I come it will not rain",
    "I will certainly come whether it rains or not",
    "I am less likely to come if it rains"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "I felt somewhat more relaxed ......",
    answer: "and tension-free as compared to earlie",
        options: [
            "but tense as compared to earlier",
    "and tense as compared to earlier",
    "as there was already no tension at all",
    "and tension-free as compared to earlier"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "He has no money now ......",
    answer: "as he has given up all his wealth",
    options: [
            "although he was very poor once",
    "as he has given up all his wealth",
    "because he was very rich once",
    "because he has received huge donation"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Because he believes in democratic principles, he always ......",
    answer: "reconciles with the majority views and gives us his own",
    options: [
            "decides all the matters himself",
    "listen to others views and enforces his own",
    "shown respect to others opinions if they match his own",

    "reconciles with the majority views and gives us his own"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 16,
        question: "MELD",
            answer: "merge",
                options: [
                    "to smooth",
                    "merge",
                    "purchase",
                    "glisten"
                ]
},

{
    numb: 17,
        question: "LYNCH",
            answer: "kill",
                options: [
                    "hang",
                    "kill",
                    "madden",
                    "shoot"
                ]
},

{
    numb: 18,
        question: "TORTURE",
            answer: "torment",
                options: [
                    "torment",
                    "chastisement",
                    "harassment",
                    "terror"
                ]
},

{
    numb: 19,
        question: "ABUNDANT",
            answer: "plenty",
                options: [
                    "ripe",
                    "cheap",
                    "plenty",
                    "absent"
                ]
},

{
    numb: 20,
        question: "ENTIRE",
            answer: "whole",
                options: [
                    "part",
                    "quater",
                    "plenty",
                    "half"
                ]
},


    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Arrange: 1. I    2. immediately  3. salary 4. my 5. want",
    answer: "15432",
    options: [
    "43152",
    "15432",
    "25143",
    "54321"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Arrange: 1. do   2. today    3. you 4. must  5. it",
    answer: "34152",
    options: [
    "34152",
    "25413",
    "12543",
    "45213"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Arrange: 1. left 2. the  3. house 4. he  5. suddenly",
    answer: "45123",
    options: [
    "12435",
    "21354",
    "45123",
    "12345"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "After the rain the weather ...... and the sun came out.",
    answer: "cleared up",
    options: [
    "cleared out",
    "cleared up",
    "cleared away",
    "cleared off"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The building comprises ...... sixty rooms.",
    answer: "no preposition needed",
    options: [
    "of",
    "onto",
    "by",
    "no preposition needed"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Namrata was found to ...... the required qualifications for the job.",
    answer: "possed",
    options: [
    "contain",
    "disclose",
    "possed",
    "acquire"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Government buildings are ...... on the Republic day.",
    answer: "illuminated",
    options: [
    "englightened",
    "lightened",
    "illuminated",
    "glowed"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "we had ...... wonderful time at the party last night.",
    answer: "such a",
    options: [
    "such a",
    "so",
    "such",
    "very"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "An employment advertisement should ...... the number of vacancies.",
    answer: "specify",
    options: [
    "provide",
    "specify",
    "contain",
    "declare"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "When varun left the cocktail party he was as ...... as a judge.",
    answer: "wise",
    options: [
    "sober",
    "drunk",
    "brave",
    "wise"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Extreme old age when a man behaves like a fool",
    answer: "dotage",
    options: [
    "imbecility",
    "dotage",
    "senility",
    "superannutation"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "One who is honourably discharged from service",
    answer: "emeritus",
    options: [
    "retired",
    "emeritus",
    "relieved",
    "emancipated"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Present opposing arguments or evidence",
    answer: "rebut",
    options: [
    "criticise",
    "rebuff",
    "rebut",
    "reprimand"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "The policy of extending a country's empire and influence",
    answer: "imperialism",
    options: [
    "imperialism",
    "internationalism",
    "capitalism",
    "communism"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "After driving professor Kumar to the museum she dropped him at his hotel.",
    answer: "After being driven to the museum, Professor Kumar was dropped at his hotel.",
    options: [
    "After being driven to the museum, Professor Kumar was dropped at his hotel.",
    "Professor Kumar was being driven dropped at his hotel.",
    "After she had driven Professor Kumar to the museum she had dropped him at his hotel.",
    "After she was driven Professor Kumar to the museum she had dropped him at his hotel."
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 16,
    question: "I remember my sister taking me to the museum.",
    answer: "I remember being taken to the museum by my sister.",
    options: [
    "I remember I was taken to the museum by my sister.",
    "I remember being taken to the museum by my sister.",
    "I remember myself being taken to the museum by my sister.",
    "I remember taken to the museum by my sister."
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Who is creating this mess?",
    answer: "By whom is this mess being created?",
    options: [
    "Who has been created this mess?",
    "By whom has this mess been created?",
    "By whom this mess is being created?",
    "By whom is this mess being created?"
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Darjeeling grows tea.",
    answer: "Tea is grown in Darjeeling.",
    options: [
    "Tea is being grown in Darjeeling.",
    "Let the tea be grown in Darjeeling.",
    "Tea is grown in Darjeeling.",
    "Tea is grows in Darjeeling."
    ]
},

    {
    numb: 19,
    question: "They have built a perfect dam across the river.",
    answer: "A perfect dam has been built by them across the river.",
    options: [
    "Across the river a perfect dam was built.",
    "A perfect dam should have been built by them.",
    "A perfect dam has been built by them across the river.",
    "Across the river was a perfect dam."
    ]
},

    {
    numb:20,
    question: "Do you imitate others?",
    answer: "Are others imitated by you?",
    options: [
    "Are others being imitated by you?",
    "Are others imitated by you?",
    "Have others being imitated by you?",
    "Were others being imitated by you?"
    ]
},

{

    question: "Extreme old age when a man behaves like a fool",
    answer: "Dotage",
    options: [
      "Imbecility",
      "Senility",
      "Dotage",
      "Superannuation"
    ]
  },
  {

    question: "The study of ancient societies",
    answer: "Archaeology",
    options: [
      "Anthropology",
      "Archaeology",
      "History",
      "Enthology"
    ]
  },
  {

    question: "A person of good understanding knowledge and reasoning power",
    answer: "Intellectual",
    options: [
      "Expert",
      "Intellectual",
      "Snob",
      "Literate"
    ]
  },
  {

    question: "A place where bees are kept in called",
    answer: "An apiary",
    options: [
      "An apiary",
      "a mole",
      "A hive",
      "A sanctury"
    ]
  },
  {

    question: "A person who speaks many languages",
    answer: "Polyglot",
    options: [
      "Linguist",
      "Monolingual",
      "Polyglot",
      "Bilingual"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Which word does NOT belong with the others?",
    answer: "mayonnaise",
    options: [
      "parsley",
      "basil",
      "dill",
      "mayonnaise"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Which word does NOT belong with the others?",
    answer: "ounch",
    options: [
      "inch",
      "ounch",
      "yard",
      "centimeter"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Odometer is to mileage as compass is to",
    answer: "direction",
    options: [
      "speed",
      "hiking",
      "needle",
      "direction"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Marathon is to race as hibernation is to",
    answer: "sleep",
    options: [
      "winter",
      "bear",
      "dream",
      "sleep"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Window is to pane as book is to",
    answer: "page",
    options: [
      "novel",
      "glass",
      "cover",
      "page"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Cup is to coffee as bowl is to",
    answer: "soup",
    options: [
      "dish",
      "soup",
      "spoon",
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    question: " Antonym of ENORMOUS",
    answer: "Tiny",
    options: [
      "Soft",
      "Tiny",
      "Average",
      "Weak"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Antonym of COMMISSIONED ",
    answer: "Terminated",
    options: [
      "Started",
      "Closed",
      "Finished",
      "Terminated"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Antonym of ARTIFICAL",
    answer: "Natural",
    options: [
      "Red",
      "Natural",
      "Truthful",
      "Solid"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Synonyms od CORPULENT",
    answer: "Obese",
    options: [
      "Lean",
      "Gaunt",
      "Emaciated",
      "Obese"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Synonyms of BRIEF",
    answer: "Short",
    options: [
      "Limited",
      "Small",
      "Little",
      "Short"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Synonyms of CANNY",
    answer: "Clever",
    options: [
      "Obstinate",
      "Handsome",
      "Clever",
      "Stout"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Fate smiles ...... those who untiringly grapple with stark realities of life.",
    answer: "on",
    options: [
      "with",
      "over",
      "on",
      "round"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "The miser gazed ...... at the pile of gold coins in front of him.",
    answer: "avidly",
    options: [
      "avidly",
      "admiringly",
      "thoughtfully",
      "earnestly"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "Catching the earlier train will give us the ...... to do some shopping.",
    answer: "chance",
    options: [
      "chance",
      "luck",
      "possibility",
      "occasion"
    ]
  },

  {
    question: "I saw a ...... of cows in the field.",
    answer: "herd",
    options: [
      "group",
      "herd",
      "swarn",
      "flock"
    ]
  },

]